ISABELLA ENRIQUEZ

Phone: (786) 566 6993 isabella.enriquez20@gmail.com

7563 Loch Ness Drive Miami, FL 33014

NBCUniversal Universal Blvd, Orlando FL 32819, USA

Dear Hiring Manager:

When I came across your advertisement looking to join the NBC Sports Group Technology & Engineering Internship program at NBCUniversal, I was immediately excited. Growing up in Miami, I was exposed to many NBCUniversal brands. My family would frequently visit the Universal Orlando Resort, my grandparents would constantly have 'Telemundo' on the TV, and my dad was a big NBA fan at home. So, NBC Sports was on regularly.

As an Information Technology student in my 3rd year, I've developed and become highly skilled in SQL, Python, and Java. As such, I would make a perfect choice for the Orlando internship in IT Support or Data Science. Additionally, obtaining an internship at the NBCUniversal company will provide me with lifelong skills and new experiences such as career prep, leadership exposure, and networking!

Thank you for considering my application. I am excited about the opportunity to bring my experience to an organization like yours, where I can contribute to its growth and success. Please don't hesitate to contact me if you need any additional information.

Sincerely,

Isabella Enriquez (786) 566-6993 <u>isabella.enriquez20@gmail.com</u>

ISABELLA ENRIQUEZ

Phone: (786) 566 6993

isabella.enriquez20@gmail.com

7563 Loch Ness Drive Miami, FL 33014

SUMMARY

A Junior at Florida International University earning a bachelor's degree in Information Technology currently working as a Student Assistant/Student Webmaster Assistant at FIU School of Computing and Information Sciences. Experience in Computer Programming, Technology and Web Design.

EDUCATION

BS Florida International University, Information Technology

Jun 2020 - Dec 2023

GPA: 3.5

Dean's List: Cum Laude

AWARDS

National Science Foundation, Florida IT Graduation Attainment Pathways Scholar Sep. 2022 Selected to participate in an NSF-funded Scholarship/Educational Research program for students in computer-related fields, providing career pathway experiences (research, internship, and/or entrepreneurship), and professional development opportunities including seminars, workshops, socials, networking events and an annual symposium.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

NSF REU, Florida International University

May. 2022 - Aug. 2022

Collaborated with Ph.D. students and professors and developed a survey paper focused on machine learning components aiding in the generalization process of adversarial machine learning; a intersection of AI and Cybersecurity.

Sponsored by the National Science Foundation and Department of Defense.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Student Assistant, Florida International University

May 2021 - Current

- Guided advising questions submitted to the KFSCIS Chat related with the CS, IT or CYB programs
- Manage/screen and control student traffic flow & routing within the advising area, particularly during rush periods (transfer orientation, registration period, last week of add/drop, etc.)

Flit-Gap Webmaster Assistant, Florida International University

Aug. 2021 - Current

- Facilitated production of high-fidelity visual design components utilizing WordPress
- Undertook maintaining and updating of site maps, user flows and wireframes for designing user navigation flow

SKILLS / ORGANIZATIONS

Skills: Design, Graphic Design, Research, Analytical Skills, Reasoning Skills, Conceptual Thinking, Communication Skills, Programming Languages (HTML, Java, Python, etc.), SQL

Organizations: Upsilon Pi Epsilon (UPE), Women in Cybersecurity (WiCyS)